I'm the daughter
of Great Yan's Chief Secretariat
and His Majesty's Grand Preceptor,
Jiang Li.
I didn't expect that Jiang Li
would reveal her identity
to stand up for the Ye family.
Isn't she afraid of being accused
of covering up for the Ye family?
Mr. Li,
the best part of the show is yet to come.
Why should we believe you?
We shouldn't be fooled
- by her lies.
- That's right.
- That's what you say.
- Yes.
Impersonating a relative
of a senior official is a felony.
Perfect timing.
Commandant Zhu is with us today.
He should be well-versed in the law.
Commandant Zhu.
Tell us. Am I right?
Is it true?
Even if you're from the Jiang family,
you can't throw your weight around.
The Jiang family is covering
for its in-laws.
It's collusion
between officials and merchants.
- It's collusion!
- Yes.
- Right!
- You are in cahoots!
What a joke.
The Jiang family is strict,
even with their daughters.
Due to my ignorance when I was little,
I was sent to Zhennv Hall
for a decade as punishment.
To uphold fairness,
my father even abandoned his daughter.
Who said I'm covering up for them? You?
Say that again!
Governor, the Ye family are in-laws
of the Chief Secretariat.
If we treat the Ye family like this,
will we…
Their daughter died in the Jiang family.
Their granddaughter was locked away
in Zhennv Hall for a decade.
Both families have severed ties.
Why would the Jiang family be concerned
about the Ye family's affairs?
Got it.
Ms. Jiang Li.
But the Ye family's Soochow brocades
are problematic indeed.
If you insist
on standing up for the Ye family,
you need to justify your statements.
Otherwise, you'd be accused
of covering up for them.
- That's right.
- Yes.
You say people die
after wearing Soochow brocades.
I'd like to ask you a question then.
How did you know
that the Soochow brocades are problematic?
All the clothing shops said so.
Everyone in Luyang knows about it.
Wasn't Mr. Ye Mingxuan
arrested by the government office?
- Right.
- Commandant Zhu.
Since when did officials
conduct investigations
purely based on hearsay?
We have evidence.
The victim's Soochow brocade
is kept at the government office.
That's why we're here to take
the one in charge of interrogation.
Did you check the victim's cause of death?
What exactly is the problem
with the Ye family's Soochow brocade?
It's yet to be investigated.
Since it's still pending investigation,
that means you don't have evidence.
Performing arrests without evidence.
Is this how careless
the Governor of Luyang works?
Mind your words, Ms. Jiang Li.
There's a murder case in Luyang,
so the Governor can investigate
and handle it.
The Ye family's Soochow brocades
are sold in the Central Plains.
I came from the capital.
Many nobles and officials
in the capital are wearing it.
If, like you said,
people who wear
the Soochow brocade may die
and it's not a coincidence,
then I suppose not only
Luyang's Soochow brocades
are problematic,
but those in other places too.
If the nobles and officials in the capital
really die after wearing Soochow brocade,
it'll certainly create chaos.
This is very serious.
It concerns the lives
of all the people of Great Yan.
Isn't it absolutely imperative
that we find out what exactly is wrong
with the Ye family's Soochow brocade?
You keep stopping us
from performing an arrest.
How can we investigate it clearly?
I've never stopped you.
The head of the Ye family is in jail now.
Everyone in Lizheng Hall
has no idea about this.
Moreover, you just said
the evidence is at the government office.
Then you should perform an autopsy,
keep a sample, and write a document,
and send it to the capital's
Office of Weaving and Dyeing.
Afterward, they will send
their officials to Luyang
to investigate the Soochow brocade case.
But what did Governor Tong do instead?
They barged into the residence
to arrest him for interrogation
but did not mention
the Office of Weaving and Dyeing at all.
I think he's the one
covering up for the Ye family.
Why didn't you ask the Office
of Weaving and Dyeing to investigate this?
Yes. What exactly is wrong
with the brocades?
Jiang Li's distortion of the truth
is really impressive.
It's more than a distortion of the truth.
Mr. Li.
She seems proficient
in throwing her weight around.
Commandant Zhu.
Please pass my message to Governor Tong.
I've already written
to my father about this.
He'll ask the Office of Weaving
and Dyeing to investigate this.
In just a few days, the Office of Weaving
and Dyeing will send people to Luyang.
By then, the truth
behind the Ye family's Soochow brocade
will be revealed.
Don't worry.
My second uncle is still detained.
The Ye family will not make off.
Commandant Zhu.
I've made myself clear.
If you insist on arresting her,
you shall face the consequences.
Retreat.
Hey, why are they leaving?
- Are they leaving?
- Right.
- Yes.
I have an idea,
but it might cost some money.
No problem.
Everyone.
The Ye family wishes to keep
the Soochow brocade you bought
as evidence.
Aside from returning your money,
we'll provide additional compensation.
- Really?
- That's great!
Sir.
Please bring out all the cash in the shop.
If it's not enough,
send someone home to get more.
Register them personally.
Yes.
Everyone, if you'd like
to return the cloth,
please line up here.
This way, please.
- Come on.
- Let's go.
One by one.
What a great show.
The beginning was mediocre,
but there was a sudden climax
toward the end.
It's worth the money
that you paid for tea, Mr. Li.
Mr. Li.
What do you think?
A mere young lady is very capable.
That's interesting indeed.
I just wonder if Chancellor Jiang
in the capital
finds out about this,
will he blame her?
If Chancellor Jiang learns
that you're involved in this,
he'll be cheering
for his daughter for fighting
against the evil forces today.
My lord.
Li Jin was right.
Jiang Li leveraged Jiang Yuanbai's name.
Isn't she scared…
She needs to leverage
Jiang Yuanbai's name.
Since Jiang Yuanbai
is the Chief Secretariat,
Tong Zhiyang will be somewhat wary.
But Tong Zhiyang
has the Li family behind him.
She's worsening the dispute
between the Jiang and Li families
without any room for maneuver.
Why?
That's her own agenda.
Come on. Drink some water.
Soothe your throat.
She saw us.
It seems like Ms. Jiang Li
is still in a rage.
Invite her again, Wen Ji.
It seems like Ms. Jiang Li
isn't willing to meet you, my lord.
Tell Ms. Jiang Li
that I enjoyed
a pot of good tea with Mr. Li.
Yes.
Did Li Jin
find this spot to watch the show
or was it you, Duke Su?
Is there a difference?
Yes.
If Li Jin found this place,
then I enjoyed putting on an act.
But if it was you…
Do you have stage fright?
I don't have stage fright.
After watching every show,
you'd always invite me over.
Your words are specious
and apathetic,
yet they hit the bull's-eye
and touch the key points,
making me owe you
and indebted to you.
Yet you
sit up high at the tea house,
showing none of your cards.
Do you really just want to watch a show?
Are you getting angry at me?
Can't I?
Your words are really pleasant then.
You…
It's better to investigate
from an elevated place.
A brothel isn't an elevated space.
Do you have to win with your words?
The person you met
at the brothel is Wu Lan.
Wu Lan?
That's a nice name.
She's the accomplice
Little Taohong mentioned.
Really?
What does this
have to do with the Ye family then?
Nothing much.
I just think
you should know about this.
All right.
Well noted on that.
Did she understand my explanation?
My lord.
I understood.
You
were not a brothel customer.
My lord is definitely not.
HELP OTHERS AND MAKE YOU
AND YOUR FAMILY HAPPY
Jiang Li is really incredible.
With just a few words,
she dominated the crowd.
Those lower-than-low
and shameless scoundrels
and despicable scums were so terrified
that they couldn't even
open their mouths.
That was how Lizheng Hall was saved.
It's all thanks to Jiang Li.
We're a family.
That's what I should do.
You're too modest, Jiang Li.
It was all thanks to you today.
It's really odd.
The officials treated us
harshly yesterday.
Yet today, they were so polite.
They even said
it was just a misunderstanding.
We thought
we'd need to spend a fortune to see him.
But he was acting oddly
and didn't take a single cent.
Governor Tong must be wary
of Chancellor Jiang.
Hence, he changed his attitude.
He's greedy
yet afraid of ruining his career.
Tong Zhiyang is truly a vile man.
No need to fear him.
But today's suppression is just temporary.
We shouldn't let down our guard.
Jiang Li.
Did you really write to your father?
Would your father really help us out?
It's too complicated
to explain to my father in words.
The letter was for Shijie.
Shijie is the new Vice Director
of the Ministry of Revenue.
If he seeks help
from the Office of Weaving and Dyeing
to conduct an investigation in Luyang,
they'll consider it for his sake.
As for my father,
I just used him to threaten Tong Zhiyang.
Otherwise, they won't let us off
easily today.
Jiang Li.
If you use your father's name like that,
will he get upset?
My father spent his whole life
building a good reputation.
If we can't leverage it to protect family
or the innocents,
it's useless.
Look at you.
You're too daring.
You acted on your own.
After you return to the capital,
your father might reprimand you.
If this goes well,
it's advantageous for my father.
He won't reprimand me.
As for Tong Zhiyang,
he hasn't dared
to make any moves recently.
As for the recalled Soochow brocade,
they need to be kept well.
The Soochow brocade
that I'm wearing is perfectly fine.
This means that the problematic
Soochow brocade just appeared recently.
Or it can also mean…
It's only found in Luyang.
At this point,
I only hope
the Office of Weaving and Dyeing
can prove
that the Soochow brocade has no problem
and clear the Ye family's name.
Jia'er.
Aunt Zhuo.
I believe
that we'll surely overcome this hurdle.
My father kept mentioning you,
Governor Tong.
He said that you're quick-witted
and capable.
It's my honor to finally meet you today.
I'm flattered.
I'm really flattered.
If this doesn't involve Chancellor Jiang,
it can surely be done.
My father has a message for you.
Don't worry about Chancellor Jiang.
You just need to do
what he told you to do.
One-tenth of the Ye family's fortune
will then
be yours.
Thank you, Mr. Li.
Thank you to Chancellor Li.
I left the capital in secret,
so I can't stay long.
That's why I must return
to the capital tomorrow.
I'll leave the rest
to you.
You and Chancellor Li can rest assured.
As long as I have Ye Mingxuan in my hands,
we can certainly
gobble up the rich Ye family.
Thank you.
I'll do my best.
LUYANG
Director.
We're already inside Luyang City.
As soon as we arrive,
I'm afraid the Ye family
and the Governor will be looking for us.
LI YU
Who should we side with?
Since the Jiang family
is the one bringing the charge,
we should consider the Jiang family first.
But we shouldn't go
against the Governor either.
Only a few dare to accuse the in-laws
of the Chief Secretariat.
The case isn't as simple as it seems.
However, if we don't provide
an explanation to Ms. Jiang Li…
When big shots fight,
the minions suffer.
The Office of Weaving and Dyeing
must not be manipulated.
Got it?
Yes.
LUYANG GOVERNMENT OFFICE
Where are the people
of the Office of Weaving and Dyeing now?
They have just arrived.
They are heading to the government office.
Great timing.
Let's show them
who's the one in charge in Luyang.
Also, Ms. Jiang Li came
to the government office.
How many are there?
There are two of them.
Well, Ms. Jiang Li.
How daring of you,
coming alone to take the man from me.
I shall meet you in person then.
BRIGHT AND CLEAR
Governor.
Excuse me for not going out
to welcome you.
You didn't inform me earlier.
Otherwise, I'd have prepared tea for you.
I was afraid that if I told you,
you wouldn't let me in.
I wouldn't do that.
As the Governor of Luyang,
all I want is for the people of Luyang
to roam freely
and live a good life in the city.
Why would I stop you from coming here?
Besides, you're a noble.
We wouldn't dare to go against you.
You're retreating to advance.
I should keep it
professional too.
If you're righteous,
you don't need
to be afraid of offending anyone.
It seems like you are trying
to suppress low-ranking officials like us
with your father's power.
Do you mean the Governor of Luyang
is afraid of high-ranking officials
and doesn't dare
to bring justice to the people?
What do you mean?
I'm begging you to bring justice
to the people, Governor Tong.
As long as the Soochow brocade case
isn't solved,
I can't live in peace.
I heard the Office of Weaving
and Dyeing officials
will arrive today.
As the relative of the victim,
of course I need to come
and explain the situation.
You're quite well-informed, Ms. Jiang Li.
Your timing is just right too.
It's nothing compared to your strategies.
You must be the Director
of the Office of Weaving and Dyeing.
My name is Tang Fan.
May I know who she is?
She's the daughter
of Chancellor Jiang, Jiang Li.
Ms. Jiang Li.
So you are Ms. Jiang Li.
My apologies for not recognizing you.
The Office has received a report
about the Ye family's
Soochow brocade case in Luyang.
Director.
The Soochow brocade
of the Ye family has caused death.
You're responsible
for matters related to weaving.
However, there is a homicide case here.
I have to investigate it.
The homicide case isn't solved yet.
Please bear with us, Director.
Any progress on the investigation?
The Ye family refuses to cooperate.
It might take some time.
But Ms. Jiang Li keeps standing here.
Perhaps she's leveraging on the Office
to make us release Mr. Ye.
Director.
Governor Tong is saying
that you have great authority
and someone can leverage it.
Governor Tong.
Mind your words.
The Ye family has never
disobeyed the Governor.
However, the Governor has kept
my uncle in custody for days.
Now, the Ye family is wrongfully accused.
The deceased couldn't rest in peace,
yet the Governor can't find anything.
You're famous
for being quick and efficient.
I'm afraid that you'll need
to stay longer in Luyang this time.
If so,
I have to report to my superior
that the Governor
is delaying the investigation.
It's important for you
to investigate the case,
yet I don't dare
to release him just like that.
If the Ye family is the culprit,
the higher-ups will surely
hold them responsible.
Since the Governor is over a barrel
to release my uncle,
I'll bring Director Tang
to investigate the other places.
You won't meddle
in the Office's investigation, right?
Of course not.
Director.
Please investigate this thoroughly
and bring justice to the people of Luyang.
That's my responsibility.
Take care. I won't see you off.
INTEGRITY CREATES AUTHORITY
So they weren't here
to ask me to release him.
They just don't want me to meddle in this.
Should I send someone to watch them?
We'd better not give them
a chance to fault us.
Let's not do anything.
Even if they were
to begin an investigation now,
they wouldn't find anything so quickly.
Let's wait for orders from the capital.
Yes.
Director.
You've traveled a long way to Luyang.
I'll escort you to rest.
Ms. Jiang,
you even praised me
for being efficient at work.
How can I rest now?
You've read my mind so well.
I'm not supposed to disturb you.
But my family is in trouble,
so I'm very worried.
Hence, I have to trouble you.
LUYANG GOVERNMENT OFFICE
This is my responsibility.
You're not troubling me in any way.
I trust that
you must have found some clues
throughout this time.
You can tell me about it.
The Soochow brocades
that caused skin rashes
after people wore them
were delivered
to the Ye family's weaving mill.
They have been left untouched,
making it easier for you to examine.
You're the expert.
We need your expertise
to solve the mystery.
If you require our assistance,
we won't ask
any questions.
You're thoughtful indeed. I'm impressed.
Come on.
Let's go
to the weaving mill.
Please.
Director.
Are these Soochow brocades problematic?
The Soochow brocade's scent
comes from incense.
Hence, it has a smoky smell
and its scent is prominent.
However, this Soochow brocade
not only smells like incense
but also has a slight hint
of sweetness.
Sweetness?
How is that possible?
There's indeed a sweet scent.
Do you know what the smell is, Ms. Ye?
I have no idea.
I feel a bit dizzy.
Li Yu. Put out the flame.
Are you all right?
It's gone once away from the fire.
There's a slight scent of burnt hair.
The burnt part is grayish
and breaks when pressed.
The original materials are fine.
The sweetness must have developed
in the later stages.
Something was added
to the incense or the final products.
It's Tuoluo from the Western Region.
Tuoluo?
Do you know it, Ms. Ye?
My father saw it
while he was traveling around.
My father also said that
Tuoluo is a type of plant
in the Western Region.
After extraction
and concoction of its juice,
it exhibits analgesic properties
when used in small amounts.
It's also hallucinogenic
and highly addictive.
However, unprocessed Tuoluo is poisonous.
A few drops can be deadly.
It causes ulceration all over the body.
You're indeed knowledgeable.
May I ask why the Soochow brocade
smells like Tuoluo?
The incense for the Soochow brocade
is handmade by my father.
All these years, nothing went wrong.
Why would we destroy our own reputation
and harm the innocent with this poison?
Ms. Ye.
Before the matter is investigated clearly,
I'm sorry,
but the Ye family
is still under suspicion.
The Tuoluo flower is rare.
It grows in a very specific environment.
Aside from the southern part
of the Western Region,
it cannot survive in other areas.
It costs at least a few taels of silver
or even dozens of taels.
The more poisonous it is,
the higher the price.
To poison people to death
using the Soochow brocade,
it'd cost over a hundred taels.
A bolt of premium Soochow brocade
is only dozens of taels.
Adding the Tuoluo flower
worth hundreds of taels
into the Soochow brocade
is not only costly
but also causes death.
A merchant definitely won't do this.
I think someone is trying
to frame the Ye family
by infusing poison
into the Soochow brocade.
We must trace its origin.
We need to find out
the source of the poison.
Since Tuoluo isn't a local plant,
it must have been brought
into Luyang through merchants.
If we investigate
the merchants entering Luyang annually,
will we be able to trace the source?
To find the source of the Tuoluo flower,
we need to report it to the authorities.
The Office of Weaving and Dyeing
can't investigate it.
I understand your concerns, Director.
However,
if you manage to find anything useful,
my father will reward you bountifully.
Director.
Won't you consider taking this chance
to befriend Chancellor Jiang?
Do you know
what the most dangerous thing is?
Greed.
Jiang Li is assuming
her father's authority
and you're taking it seriously.
I don't care who wants to investigate.
As Office of Weaving and Dyeing officials,
finding out about the Tuoluo flower
gets the job done.
Whether the culprit
is the Ye family or someone else,
it has nothing to do with me.
What should we do then?
Pretend.
Then tell Ms. Jiang Li
that we've done our best
but to no avail.
Genius.
We won't offend any parties then.
The Office of Weaving and Dyeing
obviously wants us
to investigate on our own.
If we can't find anything,
will my father be imprisoned forever?
Calm down first.
At least we have a lead
to follow now.
If only my father were around.
I know nothing about logistics.
I don't even know who to go to
for investigation.
I have a person in mind.
He might be of help.
DATONG ESCORT AGENCY
Miss, should we get a couple of guards
to go with us?
It's all right.
Come on.
Stay still. Have mercy on me.
Please spare me.
Stop shaking.
I can't aim properly.
Please. I dare not do it again.
No.
Stop.
This is fun.
It's really exciting.
- Light it.
- Stop.
Or I'll go deaf.
I did it. I stole it.
You.
I treated you well.
The escort agency is losing money.
How could you steal my wheels?
Boss.
- Stay still.
- Don't!
- Come on.
- Don't.
Shun.
Drag him outside.
Yes.
Uncle Mingyu.
You've been in Luyang for days.
Now you think of me.
I'm here today
to make a big deal with you, Uncle Mingyu.
Have a seat.
Haven't you heard
what the Ye family says about me?
You're bold to come here.
I heard that
you're not careful in making friends
and you were deceived in a major deal.
You need money now.
Did you investigate me?
Jia'er is concerned about you.
Hence, she asked around.
The Ye family is in trouble now
and they have time to care about me?
We're a family.
Why behave aggressively?
If you're here to be the peacemaker,
you can leave now.
I'm here today to ask you for a favor.
After it's done,
I'll invest money in your escort agency.
If you think I'm here
just to joke with you,
I will leave now.
What favor do you need?
- Carrots. Fresh carrots.
- Wontons.
- I'll have a look.
- Check it out.
- A bowl of wontons, sir.
- All right.
LONGXING PAWNSHOP
Well…
Do we need to dress up like this?
Didn't you say there are a lot of rules
in the black market?
If a rich brat misspoke,
it won't make things
hard for you, will it?
You're right.
- Lead the way.
- Come on.
Shoulder to shoulder.
Hanging around.
Which one?
My friend's escort carriage.
Just the two of you?
Introduce us to him.
Come on in.
Come on.
Who are we meeting with?
The head of Luyang's
ghost market, Lai Biao.
Rumor has it
that he used to serve in the army
and killed millions on the battlefield.
He's now in charge of the black market.
And I heard he can do things
the government office
can't do.
Making money with raw wheat.
Light a fire.
What does it mean?
It means that we're stupid and rich.
Let's see who the foolish one is later.
Keep quiet when we're inside.
I'll go first.
Mr. Biao. They're here.
Have a seat.
What do you want?
My master is a drug addict.
He likes the Western Region's Tuoluo
but couldn't find it in Luyang.
Please show us the way, Mr. Biao.
Tuoluo?
It's not easy to find.
My master said
if you can help us find it,
you can keep the change, Mr. Biao.
That's really generous of you.
Unfortunately, you're too late.
We just released a batch.
We can't give them to you so soon.
My master really wants it.
Don't you understand
what I said?
Tell me where the previous batch is.
I'll ask the person to sell me some.
You're not here to buy goods.
You're here to look for him.
Mr. Biao,
there's no harm in telling me
who that person is.
To be honest,
officials from the capital
are investigating him.
If you're dragged into this,
it'll be bad.
You dare to threaten me?
Why would I be scared
of officials from the capital?
Liu.
Send the guests off.
Filter my guests from now on.
Let's go.
Never mind then.
Let's think of another way.
What a joke.
You're the head of Luyang's black market.
Your customer is offering a deal,
yet you're chasing us out.
I'm sure you're just
incapable of getting it done.
How dare you!
There are dos and don'ts
in the ghost market.
Asking for the buyer's details
is against my rules.
Rules?
If he dares to buy it,
is he afraid of being discovered?
What if I insist
on getting an answer today?
You
can name your condition.
You're brave indeed.
Then I'll give you a chance
according to the rules.
Do you dare to take up the challenge?
What do you want?
Your friend is familiar with it.
Ask him.
The Golden Water Formation challenge.
Golden Water Formation?
My lord.
Wu Lan sent a message saying Chu Lan
will arrive in Luyang tonight.
They'll meet
at the west district's residence.
Be prepared.
Tell her to buy us
as much time as possible.
Yes.
My lord, there's one more thing.
Jiang Li and Ye Mingyu
went to the black market disguised.
Why?
They probably went to seek Lai Biao's help
for the Ye family's Soochow brocade.
Judging by their looks,
they won't give up if they don't succeed.
I even heard
that Lai Biao has
the Golden Water Formation rule too.
Well…
Golden Water Formation?
What formation is it?
You can think of it
as a group of people
drinking a lot together.
The Golden Water Formation begins!
The so-called Golden Water Formation
is a drinking game.
The dice total determines the winner.
If you lose, you need to drink.
According to the rules,
if they get drunk first,
they will get things done.
LOSE, WIN
Liu wins.
- Drink!
- It's all right.
Since we're doing
the Golden Water Formation challenge,
- I'm going all out.
- Drink!
- Look at those weaklings.
- I can easily defeat ten of them.
- Drink!
- Great!
- Nice!
Another round!
This mister wins.
- Drink!
The two of us must drink two bowls.
There are so many of them,
yet they drink two bowls too.
- Cool!
- That's the Golden Water Formation's rule.
We need to defeat
thrice the number of challengers
in order to compete with Lai Biao.
Third round.
- Drink!
- Drink up!
Stand up.
You can't drink anymore?
Who else is there?
Last round.
Mr. Biao is here.
- He's here? Mr. Biao!
- He came? Mr. Biao!
- Uncle Mingyu.
- Mr. Biao!
- Can you still drink?
- I'm fine.
- Mr. Biao!
- Don't worry.
- Mr. Biao.
You're rather lucky.
No one was able to defeat us.
You're the only one left.
I don't want to bully you
since you're outnumbered.
Just tell us…
Uncle Mingyu.
Wake up.
You can't collapse now.
What is this?
Hang on for two rounds.
Wake me up with this later.
It hurts.
Uncle Mingyu.
Hold on.
We're not done yet.
If you lose,
honor your word.
He said I won't honor my word.
I, Lai Biao, always honor my word.
Start!
Mr. Biao wins!
- Mr. Biao!
You're really daring, sir.
You dare to challenge my formation
with only one partner.
I'll drink with you in this round.
- As expected of Mr. Biao.
- Yes.
From now on, I won't show you any mercy.
- Drink!
Your dice is problematic.
Let's change it then.
Truth be told,
I've been playing the dice for ages.
I know the numbers just by listening.
You can't defeat me.
Hold on.
You can't beat me at drinking
or playing the dice.
Why are you wasting your time?
I'm not drunk yet.
When you get drunk,
who will bring you home?
- I…
- Are you going to spend the night here?
I'll bring him home.
Who's that?
Drink as much as you want.
If you get drunk, I'll bring you home.
I thought at this moment,
you would say
that you'd drink on my behalf.
- If you beg me, I--
- Please.
You're really shameless.
Is this considered a favor?
No.
Good.
You…
What about me?
Don't you chicken out.
Drink until he drops.
Is he
your savior
or your enemy?
It's none of your business.
I'm competing with him.
Who are you?
It's no fun playing with him.
Let's have a good game together,
General Biao.
Do you know each other?
He was my father's nemesis.
He was involved in a case later on
and became a bandit.
I didn't expect him
to become the head of this market.
Consider me unlucky
to fall into your hands.
Do whatever you want
with me.
Is your father
Xiao Minghan?
That's right.
You both like to play the hero
rescuing damsels in distress.
I'm warning you.
According to our rules,
if you join halfway through,
you need to double up your drinks.
You roll the dice.
I'm very lucky today.
Start.
Mr. Biao wins.
- Mr. Biao!
- Drink!
If this continues,
we can't win even if there are ten of him.
What should I do?
Truth be told,
I've been playing the dice for ages.
I know the numbers just by listening.
Hang on for two rounds.
Wake me up with this later.
It's my turn to counterattack.
You roll it.
Do you trust me now?
I'm borrowing your luck.
What are you doing?
I'm feeling a bit sleepy.
I'm just trying to stay awake.
- You…
- The Golden Water Formation
doesn't prohibit fireworks, right?
Open it.
The mister wins!
Why are you only using this idea now?
What did you say?
Are you trying to get me drunk?
Why would I do that?
You're so suspicious.
Are you not upset now?
What are you mumbling?
Again!
Another round.
PROMOTE GOOD AND CONDEMN EVIL
That's enough!
You
won.
What?
Say that again.
- What?
- What was that?
Enough is enough.
If this continues,
everyone will lose their hearing.
Can you tell us
who bought the Tuoluo flower now?
Wait a minute.
I want to have a talk
with your defeated opponent first.
Are you here for me
or to save that young lad?
Both.
I want to ask a favor, General Biao.
Why should I help you?
My father saved your life before.
You're just and frank
and never got involved
in partisan disputes.
You were framed and imprisoned
after offending Li Zhongnan,
then exiled to Nanjiang.
My father knew that you were innocent.
He admired your spirit, so he let you go.
And this time, I'm dealing
with Li Zhongnan's party.